pooldawg.com 2006-06-29

# - Help section

[Pool Dawg](http://www.pooldawg.com/?PHPSESSID=cf28c5559bfb6214b3a214912d78d2be) :: Help zone

|   Shipping & Customer Service  
---  
  
**Customer Service Information**

**Contact Us**

PoolDawg.com, Inc.  
PO Box 552  
Lafayette CO 80026  
866-THE-DAWG

**Customer Service Hours**  
Monday through Friday 10:30AM to 7:00PM EST. 

We will always respond to your questions and concerns with in 24 hours.

Phone: 866.THE.DAWG (866.843.3294)  
Fax: 720.214.2668  
E-mail: info@pooldawg.com

**30 Day Money Back Guarantee**  
Pool Dawg offers a 30-day money back guarantee on any new and unused product purchased from Pool Dawg. We want you to be satisfied. No restocking fees, no hassles. Cues must be unchalked and in original condition to receive full refund or credit. 

**Product Warranty**  
Pool Dawg will honor a one-year warranty from all manufacturer defects. Claims after one year are subject to manufacturer policies and their approval. Special note: Warping once a cue is chalked is not considered a defect.

**How To Order Through the Web**  
Choose your product or products:  
1\. Choose an item you would like to purchase and double click the image or product name to open the product details page.   
2\. Select the appropriate weight; size or color and quantity.  
3\. Click “add to cart”.   
4\. Add any additional items by clicking the Products Navigation buttons.

**When you are ready to check out:**  
1\. Click the “Purchase” button on the shopping cart page or select “check out” button at the bottom right of any page. At this point you are on secure pages for the balance of the transaction.  
2\. Enter your billing information / shipping information   
3\. Click the “Submit” button  
4\. Verify your billing information and product information.   
5\. Enter your credit card information where requested. From this page you can print a receipt. Your receipt includes your order number.  
6\. Select “Check Out”. 

**Order Confirmation via email**  
1\. You will receive order confirmation once your credit card has been charged.  
2\. We will send you a tracking number once your order has shipped.

**How To Order Off Line**

Call us direct with your order  
866.THE.DAWG (866.843.3294)

**Track Your Order**  
Tracking your order from Pool Dawg is simple! We will email you a tracking number once your product/s has been shipped. To check on the status of your order got to [ www.ups.com](http://www.ups.com/) and enter your tracking number. If you encounter any problems call us at 866.THE.DAWG (866.843.3294)

**Payment Options**  
Pool Dawg accepts VISA, MasterCard, Discover, American Express and PayPal.

**Return and Exchange Policy**  
We want you to be happy with your purchase from Pool Dawg. If for some reason you are unhappy let us know and we will make every effort to make it right. 

We offer a 30-day money back guarantee on any new and unused products. Any new product containing a manufacturer defect will be replaced, credited or refunded at its original purchase price. Cues must be unchalked and in original condition to receive full refund or credit.

Used products will be evaluated as the appropriate manufacturer’s policy states.   
Special note: Warping once a cue is chalked is not considered a defect.

**To process a return or exchange:**

1\. Please call us at 866.843.3294 or email us at info@pooldawg.com. We will issue a UPS call tag upon hearing from you. **Please note tha twe cannot offer call tag service to countries outside of the United States**.  
2\. Pack your product/s securely and in appropriate packaging. Damage to products due to poor packaging can affect your refund.  
3\. Once we receive your product, we will process a credit to your credit card within 24hours of our evaluation of the product/s. Please allow additional time for the credit of your return to show up on your statement. Purchases made by check must wait for the original check to clear prior to receiving your money back. You can receive a store credit once the product returned is received and evaluated.  
4\. If for some reason there is an error on our part with the shipping process we will arrange for the product to be picked up and returned to you at our expense.   
5\. If your package is damaged due to the shipping company please contact us within 24 hours at info@pooldawg.com or 866.843.3294. You will be instructed on the procedures to have the product returned to us. We will insure that you receive the proper credit and/or replacement of the product.

**Shipping Options**

Place your in-stock order before 4:00 pm EST Monday through Friday, and your order will be rushed out the door that same day. As long as your request is in stock we guarantee the very best turn-around time. If for some reason we don’t get it out that day, we’ll make sure to contact you in the event of a stock outage or other delay.

Pool Dawg offers FREE SHIPPING on all orders over $50. This offer is for ground service to the 48 contiguous United States using UPS or USPS.

Pool Dawg ships products all over the world. Please note that in some cases where we are not able to verify the billing address of the credit card, you will be asked to provide us with additional infomration via fax. Please be aware that you are responsible for any applicable duties and taxes from your local government. Address any concerns to info@pooldwg.com

Regular ground shipping within the 48 contiguous United States takes any where from 4 to 6 business days. Time in transit quotes and scheduled delivery dates can be located at the UPS web site once you receive confirmation of shipment and a tracking number has been issued.

Shipping charges for the 48 contiguous United States may be calculated by adding items to the shopping cart, entering your zip code, choosing a shipping method and clicking the calculate shipping button. Please be advised that PoolDawg.com, Inc. only collects sales tax for orders originating from the state of Colorado. Customers placing orders from any other state or country are responsible for any taxes or tariffs that their local governments may apply. 

**Our Commitment to Privacy**  
Our Privacy Policy was developed as an extension of our commitment to combine the highest-quality products and services with the highest level of integrity in dealing with our customers. The Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, use and safeguard the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site and our products and services. This statement will be continuously assessed against new technologies, business practices and our customers' needs.

**What Information Do We Collect?**  
When you visit Pool Dawg you may provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis and Web site use information collected on an aggregate basis as you and others browse our web site.  
1\. Personal Information You Choose to Provide  
Credit Card Information   
If you choose to purchase products or services from Pool Dawg, you may need to give personal information and authorization to obtain information from various credit services. For example, you may need to provide the following information:  
· Name  
· Mailing address  
· Email address  
· Credit card number  
· Home and business phone number

**Email Information**  
In addition to providing the foregoing information to our partners, if you choose to correspond further with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses. We provide the same protections for these electronic communications that we employ in the maintenance of information received by mail and telephone.  
2\. Web Site Use Information  
Similar to other commercial web sites, our Web site utilizes a standard technology called "cookies" (see explanation below, "What Are Cookies?") and Web server logs to collect information about how our Web site is used. Information gathered through cookies and Web server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at our Web site, and the Web sites visited just before and just after our Web site. This information is collected on an aggregate basis. None of this information is associated with you as an individual.  
How Do We Use the Information That You Provide to Us?  
Broadly speaking, we use personal information for purposes of administering our business activities, providing customer service and making available other products and services to our customers and prospective customers. Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to our Web site, new services and special offers we think you will find valuable. The lists used to send you product and service offers are developed and managed under our traditional corporate standards designed to safeguard the security and privacy of our customers’ personal information. As a customer, you will be given the opportunity, at least once annually, to notify us of your desire not to receive these offers.

**What Are Cookies?  
**Cookies are a feature of Web browser software that allows Web servers to recognize the computer used to access a Web site. Cookies are small pieces of data that are stored by a user’s Web browser on the user’s hard drive. Cookies can remember what information a user accesses on one Web page to simplify subsequent interactions with that Web site by the same user or to use the information to streamline the user’s transactions on related Web pages. This makes it easier for a user to move from Web page to Web page and to complete commercial transactions over the Internet. Cookies should make your online experience easier and more personalized.  
How Do We Use Information We Collect from Cookies?  
We use Web site browser software tools such as cookies and Web server logs to gather information about our Web site users’ browsing activities, in order to constantly improve our Web site and better serve our customers. This information assists us to design and arrange our Web pages in the most user-friendly manner and to continually improve our Web site to better meet the needs of our customers and prospective customers.  
Cookies help us collect important business and technical statistics. The information in the cookies lets us trace the paths followed by users to our Web site as they move from one page to another. Web server logs allow us to count how many people visit our Web site and evaluate our Web site’s visitor capacity. We do not use these technologies to capture your individual email address or any personally identifying information about you although they do permit us to send focused online banner advertisements or other such responses to you.   
Notice of New Services and Changes  
Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to our Web site, new services and special offers we think you will find valuable. As our customer, you will be given the opportunity to notify us of your desire not to receive these offers by clicking on a response box when you receive such an offer or by sending us an email request at info@pooldawg.com   
How Do We Secure Information Transmissions?  
When you send confidential personal credit card information to us on our Web site, a secure server software, which we have licensed, encrypts all information you input before it is sent to us. The information is scrambled en route and decoded once it reaches our Web site.  
Other email that you may send to us may not be secure unless we advise you that security measures will be in place prior to your transmitting the information. For that reason, we ask that you do not send confidential information such as Social Security or account numbers to us through an unsecured email.   
How Do We Protect Your Information?  
Information Security. We utilize encryption/security software to safeguard the confidentiality of personal information we collect from unauthorized access or disclosure and accidental loss, alteration or destruction.  
Evaluation of Information Protection Practices. Periodically, our operations and business practices are reviewed for compliance with corporate policies and procedures governing the security, confidentiality and quality of our information.  
Employee Access, Training and Expectations. Our corporate values, ethical standards, policies and practices are committed to the protection of customer information. In general, our business practices limit employee access to confidential information, and limit the use and disclosure of such information to authorized persons, processes and transactions.  
How Can You Access and Correct Your Information?  
You may request access to all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain in our database by emailing info@pooldawg.com   
Do We Disclose Information to Outside Parties?  
We may provide aggregate information about our customers, sales, Web site traffic patterns and related Web site information to our affiliates or reputable third parties, but this information will not include personally identifying data, except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy.  
What About Legally Compelled Disclosure of Information?  
We may disclose information when legally compelled to do so, in other words, when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires it or for the protection of our legal rights.  
What About Other Web Sites Linked to Our Web Site?  
We are not responsible for the practices employed by Web sites linked to or from our Web site nor the information or content contained therein. Often links to other Web sites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to the users of our Web site.

**Your Credit Card Protects You**  
Your credit card offers online fraud protection click here for more information.

Discover [Click Here](http://www2.discovercard.com/simple_secure/)

Mastercard [Click Here](http://www.mastercard.com/general/zero_liability.html)

Visa [Click Here](http://www.usa.visa.com/personal/secure_with_visa/)

AMEX [Click Here](http://www10.americanexpress.com/sif/cda/page/0,1641,5962,00.asp?link=benefits)
